[ ♪ upbeat music ♪ ]
F-35.
First is the motor lock.
Then propeller. Just do what I
did.
Wing panel. Helium.
Inactive apply at center.
Half wedge down one times two equals two.
Motor lock again.
Half wedge down glass.
Control surface one times one equals one
hehe.
Make sure the green arrow is at the
bottom.
Cylinder. Delta wing one times two.
Tiny landing gear. Please be aware. Be
sure to rotate.
Pontoons front. If you don't have
pontoons, you can use the cutter, but the
balance will be affected. Cutter.
Disconnector. Pyramid wedge.
Camera. Make sure the green arrow is at
the bottom.
Trap door.
Half wedge. Wing panel one
times one.
Half wedge. Half quarter wedge
up.
Be sure to imitate it lol. Select metal
in materials.
Follow what I do. If you do not do this,
the balance may be affected.
All red color metal.
Controls.
How to control: first double-click G.
Always hold W when flying. Up to fly up,
down to fly down.
A to turn left, D to turn right.
And don't click G while flying like a
fool.
W to move forward, S to slow speed.
Let's try to land.
Yay! Another one.
Lol. [ ♪ upbeat music ♪ ] That's all guys. Bye.
Thank you for
watching.